Hello there!

My name is Logan Coning. I am a Web Developer by trade and tech enthusiast by nature.

I began my journey in the web industry in late 2018 by way of the Front-end TechDegree from Treehouse. I immediately became fascinated with learning and advancing my career in this trade. I'm passionate about technology - not a specific framework or language. In this line of work it's about adaptation, and what works best for the project. I'm open to learning any stack if it works.

My motto as a developer is if I'm not learning something new daily, I'm not in the game. I love learning, and am always working to become the best developer I can be. I am a maker - I enjoy creating In my career and after hours. I believe in shipping quality code and working in flow.

I have experience with a variety of projects and project deployment. I have used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create front end applications and static pages that demonstrate a responsive mobile-first approach, cross-compatibility with modern browsers, and verified valid programming. While my experience level would indicate I am starting as entry-level, I can quickly adapt and learn new technologies in a flash. If you are interested in checking out some of my work, take a look at my Github page linked on my resume.

I care deeply about the code I write and the effect my work has on the product. I enjoy interaction with clients and seeing the joy they get when they get the application they've been wanting.

I am a Frontend developer by trade, however I seem to have a knack for solving technological problems. I enjoy troubleshooting computers and computer networks and implementing equipment and infrastructure that streamlines performance and usability.

That said - I think I align with what you're doing and believe I would be a great fit technology and culture wise. If I'm not a perfect match for this position I am open to other positions that may better fit my qualifications.

Looking forward to hearing back.

Kind Regards,

Logan R. Coning

LinkedIn- linkedin.com/in/logan-coning-3b046517a

Portfolio- https://www.loganconing.com Github- https://github.com/lcohio

Logan Coning 1018 E. Canal St Troy, OH

Phone: (937)-703-8005 | Email: coninglogan@gmail.com

Front-end web developer with the intent of obtaining employment for an organization that values individual expression and creativity and cultivates an environment conducive to learning and growth. I want to channel my passion for writing code into creating clean, functional, and well-tested commercial web pages and applications.

#Skills

Front-End Source Control FrameWorks Dev Tools

Javascript ES6 / jQuery CSS / SASS / LESS Git Github Bootstrap

VS Code Slack

HTML5

#Professional Experience Web Developer

Nov 2018 - current

Work with clients to achieve suitable information and content for their website

Hand-code responsive web pages and applications using well-organized markup and styling

Implement interactive programming using JavaScript and jQuery

Fetch and load API data synchronously into the project

Utilize version control software to achieve a unified workflow

Metcon, LTD / Sales Estimator

Jul 2015 - Mar 2019 : Bradford, OH

Compute volume of materials needed on commercial construction projects.

Calculate hours of labor required for completion.

Provide support & troubleshooting of computers, computer software, file and asset hosting, internal and external networking, and mobile devices.

#Education

High School Diploma (GED)

Treehouse / Front-End Web Development TechDegree

2018 - 2019